

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Amk Ave 4, Blk 618, #07-1061, Ang Mo Kio, 560618, Singapore 92483989 Lerwinloh22@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH 22/03/2002 Singapore

Singaporean

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word, Powerpoint, Excel

Google Docs, Slides, Excel

Tableau

Figma, Wireframe Tool

Splunk

MS SQL

HTML5

CSS

JavaScript

Python Programming

C# Programming

Swift Programming

SOFT SKILLS

Effective Time Management Skills

Proficient in Communication

Strong Leadership Qualities

Good Analytical Skills

Strong Team Coordination

PROFILE

With a striving passion and portraying a motivated mindset for Business & Financial Technology, I aim to solve real-world complex issues with the aid of technology. I am skilful in multiple programming languages, as well as the logic involved. I am also capable of adapting to new working environments due to ample different working experiences. Hence, equipped with both business thinking and coding logic, I am able to bring new business and technological solutions.

WEBSITE

For the best experience, visit www.lerwinloh.com to explore my carefully curated portfolio, built from the ground up. This Full-Stack project leverages Google Firebase for seamless data storage and management, Express.js as the backend framework for efficient server-side logic and routing, and Node.js as the runtime environment for executing backend JavaScript code. On the front end, Handlebars powers dynamic view rendering, ensuring a smooth user experience. The site is hosted on Render, offering a fully managed infrastructure with automatic scaling, continuous deployment from my Git repository, and built-in SSL security. Additionally, it is fully responsive and optimized for viewing across all devices.

EDUCATION

Diploma With Merit, Nanyang Polytechnic (GPA 4.0)

2019 — 2023

• Edusave merit bursary, 2020

Secondary School, Mayflower

2015 — 2018

- N Level Certificate (Net 6 points).
- · Co-Curricular Activity: NPCC, Staff Sergeant.
- Edusave scholarship, 2017.
- Edusave scholarship, 2018.
- Edusave eagles award, 2018.

Primary School, Da Qiao Primary

2009 - 2014

PSLE Certificate

AWARDS

Awarded Director List, Semester 2

2022 - 2023

Top 15% of students who excel academically in the semester in a full-time diploma are placed on the Director's List.

Awarded Director List, Semester 1

2022 — 2023

Awarded Director List, Semester 2

2021 - 2022

Awarded Director List, Semester 1

2021 — 2022

Awarded Director List, Semester 2

2020 — 2021

Awarded Director List, Semester 1

2020 — 2021

Positive Mindset

Resourceful

Independent

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Nanobee Co-Founder, Full Stack Developer

NOVEMBER 2022 — APRIL 2024

- Nanobee is a pre-seed stage start-up started by students from NUS SoC, NYP Business, and IT schools with experiences in the start-up scene, such as Start-up Development at EnterpriseSG, Business Development at Grab and MAS and we have a current headcount of 7. We aim to streamline the nano-influencer process to help small businesses grow by using Artificial Intelligence (AI) to profile and match suitable influencers to business campaigns, develop improved tools for businesses to manage campaigns and enable new ad-hoc services that influencers on our platform can provide that are not currently being offered by our competitors. We are currently backed by Nanyang Polytechnic's \$10,000 JumpStart grant (2 nd Cohort, 2022)
- My current role is to develop and maintain Nanobee's web application frontend and the back-end systems such as, curating Nanobee's intuitive UI/UX, Cloud Database, system logic, and perform crucial analyses.
- Skills Used: NodeJs Framework, JavaScript, Html, CSS, Django.

Associate Researcher Intern at Procter & Gamble (Data Science & Modelling), Biopolis

SEPTEMBER 2022 — FEBRUARY 2023

• I have successfully curated a brand and product detection model, backed by sophisticated algorithms to accurately identify specific brands and products. This model targets skincare and haircare products that the consumers are using daily. The aim of this is to aid in automatically identifying and performing passive analysis on the products the consumers in-the-wild is using. This model also allows identified products to be mapped with useful information such as the ingredients, product form, market origin, etc, which will aid in product understanding. The superior brand detection model is validated with a precision accuracy of 95.86% and a recall accuracy of 96.06%.

Stock Replenisher at NTUC, Ang Mo Kio

AUGUST 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2021

- Remained informed and up to date on the current stock and offerings.
- · Organized and maintained stock orders prior to shelving.
- Worked with superiors and colleagues with an upbeat attitude.
- Utilized excellent organizational skills.

Retail Sales Associate at Hush Puppies, Novena/Jewel

AUGUST 2019 — APRIL 2020

- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Delivered a high level of customer engagement and successfully forged meaningful relationships with customers.
- Liaised with customers and recommended specific products and specials, aligning with individual's needs, requirements and specifications.

Waiter at Marks & Spencer, Orchard

JANUARY 2019 — MARCH 2019

- Greeted new customers, discussed specials, took orders and build connections with guests.
- Dependable and friendly professional with cash & credit registry services at the counter front.
- Illustrated good time management skills to juggle customers' needs and wants simultaneously.

Sales Promoter at Raffles Paint, Serangoon

DECEMBER 2018 — JANUARY 2019

- Communicated clearly and displayed positive energy and professional outward appearance to foster a welcoming environment.
- Applied promotional tools to build product awareness, create customer interest and stimulate product demand.
- Able to handle and communicate with different people effectively.
- Resolved customer issues and concerns by listening attentively, identifying root issues and implementing the best resolution possible.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Development with NodeJs, School Project

APRIL 2022 — AUGUST 2022

This project focuses on creating a Business to Customer (B2C) web application that facilitates an ecommerce shop, admin management, and supplier management features. This shoe commerce shop called, "ShoeCraft" is built to demo my intuitiveness and programming skills. My team and I have successfully created a superior ecommerce platform that mimics a full cycle from customer purchase, order management, aftersales management, discount management, admin management, product management, and even mimicked supplier interactions through code.

Business Innovation Project with NodeJs, School Project

APRIL 2022 — AUGUST 2022

With the problem statement, "How can you help migrants create personal digital identity that can be trusted and accepted globally?" given from PolyFinTech 100 API Hackathon 2022, my team and I came up with an cutting edge solution, which we were also nominated and represented NYP for the PolyFinTech 100 API Hackathon 2022 competition. Utilising this problem statement, My team and I created a viable proof of concept (POC) which uses cutting edge technologies such as blockchain implementations and AI Automation features.

E-Business Project with C# & ASP.NET, School Project

NOVEMBER 2021 — FEBRUARY 2022

Using C# and ASP.NET, this project is developed with dynamic and database-driven web applications such as SQL. Security and Mimicking "Automation" are also two major components that are implemented into the E-business Website.

App Development Project, School Project

NOVEMBER 2020 — FEBRUARY 2021

This project focuses on Business to Business (B2B) that makes use of application web services. My team and I created a website called, "Candy Floriculture" using Python, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This website is developed based on the python flask framework and it aims to enable consumers to make transactions seamlessly at their own comfort. Our team have outperformed ourselves and achieved Distinction for this project.

App Development With Swift, Diploma Plus Project

 ${\rm APRIL}~2021~-~{\rm AUGUST}~2021$

This project focuses on creating a Mobile Application on an IOS platform using swift and MySQL language. My friend and I have created a mobile application that targets the booking of Gym facilities for Nanyang Polytechnic.

Business Analytics Project, School Project

APRIL 2021 — AUGUST 2021

My team and I have successfully applied visualization concepts and techniques in the development of a business analytic and business intelligence application, to support the hypothesis, "The ease of house ownership in Singapore is increasing". Our team have achieved Distinction for integrating database and Python programming in Data Cleaning and Extraction.

COURSES

Robotics Process Automation Development (RPA), Diploma Plus

(Poly Year 3, Semester 1)

- This certification is under the Diploma plus program at Nanyang Polytechnic
- I have achieved a grade of A and have demonstrated proficient use of the UiPath Studio software application.

Machine Data Analytics & Operational Intelligence (Splunk), Diploma Plus (Poly Year 2, Semester 2)

- This certification is under the Diploma plus program at Nanyang Polytechnic
- I have achieved a grade of Distinction and have demonstrated proficient use of the Splunk software application.

App Development with Swift, Diploma Plus

(Poly Year 2, Semester 1)

- This certification is under the Diploma plus program at Nanyang Polytechnic.
- I have achieved a grade of A and portrayed a driving passion for Swift programming.